[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 59, "question": "If you had been there when it was happening and you saw team after team doing the same thing, do you have any power to actually do something?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "been", "there", "when", "it", "was", "happening", "and", "you", "saw", "team", "after", "team", "doing", "the", "same", "thing", ",", "do", "you", "have", "any", "power", "to", "actually", "do", "something", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "No, not as a --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "as", "a", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 82, "question": "What is your view about that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 83, "answer": "Yes, I'm on reconstructed on the subject.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "'m", "on", "reconstructed", "on", "the", "subject", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "Should they be?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "they", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "Personally, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Personally", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Wouldn't that -- wouldn't that a one-hit, do more effective work with this than what's going on at the moment?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "that", "--", "would", "n't", "that", "a", "one-hit", ",", "do", "more", "effective", "work", "with", "this", "than", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "at", "the", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Yes, you're right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "'re", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["U.K."]}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 111, "question": "Is he?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 112, "answer": "Well, you know, the lovely thing about the games in the U.K. is we've had the big -- you know, we've had the national pop (ph) game.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "lovely", "thing", "about", "the", "games", "in", "the", "U.K.", "is", "we", "'ve", "had", "the", "big", "--", "you", "know", ",", "we", "'ve", "had", "the", "national", "pop", "(", "ph", ")", "game", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "Who do you think is?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "Well, you have to say that winning 19 medals or whatever he managed last night makes him certainly the most successful and prolific medal winner.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "have", "to", "say", "that", "winning", "19", "medals", "or", "whatever", "he", "managed", "last", "night", "makes", "him", "certainly", "the", "most", "successful", "and", "prolific", "medal", "winner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Well, yes, I'm from track and field.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", ",", "I", "'m", "from", "track", "and", "field", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "Who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "Well, modesty probably prohibits me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "modesty", "probably", "prohibits", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "Would you?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "For snuffing you out that time?", "question_tokens": ["For", "snuffing", "you", "out", "that", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "Is there a feeling that if she was an American or a British swimmer, we wouldn't even be debating it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "a", "feeling", "that", "if", "she", "was", "an", "American", "or", "a", "British", "swimmer", ",", "we", "would", "n't", "even", "be", "debating", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Surely.", "answer_tokens": ["Surely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "That they are now prepared to play by the rules of the Olympic Games?", "question_tokens": ["That", "they", "are", "now", "prepared", "to", "play", "by", "the", "rules", "of", "the", "Olympic", "Games", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Yes, it is one of the top trending topics, especially in the micro blogging sites here.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "is", "one", "of", "the", "top", "trending", "topics", ",", "especially", "in", "the", "micro", "blogging", "sites", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 218, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 219, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "How exciting has it's been for you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "exciting", "has", "it", "'s", "been", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBG", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, I -- I love to see, you know, incredible performances.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "--", "I", "love", "to", "see", ",", "you", "know", ",", "incredible", "performances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "Have you come through all the traumas and dramas of what went on?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "come", "through", "all", "the", "traumas", "and", "dramas", "of", "what", "went", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "The mere fact that both of you look so fit, and healthy and well, and happy is all you need to see, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["The", "mere", "fact", "that", "both", "of", "you", "look", "so", "fit", ",", "and", "healthy", "and", "well", ",", "and", "happy", "is", "all", "you", "need", "to", "see", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "JJ", "CC", "RB", ",", "CC", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 267, "question": "ORGAN: Even now, do you still have to take a huge amount of pills a day?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Even", "now", ",", "do", "you", "still", "have", "to", "take", "a", "huge", "amount", "of", "pills", "a", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "RB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 268, "answer": "It's not quite as many.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "quite", "as", "many", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Were you angered when the Chic-fil-A boss said what he said?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "angered", "when", "the", "Chic-fil-A", "boss", "said", "what", "he", "said", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, you know, I'm not real political, you know, but I know what's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "real", "political", ",", "you", "know", ",", "but", "I", "know", "what", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "Never mind the views about same-sex marriage, right?", "question_tokens": ["Never", "mind", "the", "views", "about", "same-sex", "marriage", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Where are you on all of this?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "on", "all", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "You know, I am so thankful that I was in a sport that we didn't have that really as an issue.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "am", "so", "thankful", "that", "I", "was", "in", "a", "sport", "that", "we", "did", "n't", "have", "that", "really", "as", "an", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 337, "question": "When you went back and dived again and you came back up, and your head bounced up through the water, what was going through your mind?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "went", "back", "and", "dived", "again", "and", "you", "came", "back", "up", ",", "and", "your", "head", "bounced", "up", "through", "the", "water", ",", "what", "was", "going", "through", "your", "mind", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "You know --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "The first thing you thought?", "question_tokens": ["The", "first", "thing", "you", "thought", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "Well, going through something like that, OK, I hit my head on the board.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "going", "through", "something", "like", "that", ",", "OK", ",", "I", "hit", "my", "head", "on", "the", "board", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Greg"]}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "You know?", "question_tokens": ["You", "know", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Greg, it's been a real pleasure to see you.", "answer_tokens": ["Greg", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "real", "pleasure", "to", "see", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Who would be first choice?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "first", "choice", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, I look at it differently.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "look", "at", "it", "differently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 413, "question": "Did you ever in your era come up against anybody who you thought you possibly couldn't beat?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "in", "your", "era", "come", "up", "against", "anybody", "who", "you", "thought", "you", "possibly", "could", "n't", "beat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 414, "answer": "I looked at it in a different way.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "looked", "at", "it", "in", "a", "different", "way", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 430, "question": "Are we better off today than we were when Ben Johnson got caught?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "better", "off", "today", "than", "we", "were", "when", "Ben", "Johnson", "got", "caught", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 431, "answer": "What's sad about it is that it's never going to end.", "answer_tokens": ["What", "'s", "sad", "about", "it", "is", "that", "it", "'s", "never", "going", "to", "end", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "PERSON": ["Ben Johnson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 453, "question": "Of all the great moments you've had, what was the best for you?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "great", "moments", "you", "'ve", "had", ",", "what", "was", "the", "best", "for", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 454, "answer": "Oh my goodness, you can't top --", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "my", "goodness", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "top", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 458, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 459, "answer": "Well, because it was the first one, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "because", "it", "was", "the", "first", "one", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Is there anything quite like the Olympics?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "quite", "like", "the", "Olympics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "The Olympics are unique.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Olympics", "are", "unique", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "Did you ever have that in your time?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "ever", "have", "that", "in", "your", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 488, "question": "When you were competing at your very best for America and Ronald Reagan was president, did you ever imagine in your lifetime that you would have an African-American president?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "were", "competing", "at", "your", "very", "best", "for", "America", "and", "Ronald", "Reagan", "was", "president", ",", "did", "you", "ever", "imagine", "in", "your", "lifetime", "that", "you", "would", "have", "an", "African-American", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "RB", "JJS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 489, "answer": "No, I didn't.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBN", ":", "VB", "VBZ", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Is it easier or harder to be a black man or woman in America these days?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "easier", "or", "harder", "to", "be", "a", "black", "man", "or", "woman", "in", "America", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I don't think we became more racist, but I think people woke up the next day and said wait, wait, what happened; let's go back to the old times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "became", "more", "racist", ",", "but", "I", "think", "people", "woke", "up", "the", "next", "day", "and", "said", "wait", ",", "wait", ",", "what", "happened", ";", "let", "'s", "go", "back", "to", "the", "old", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "What does it mean A, to compete for your country, for America, and B, to win?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "it", "mean", "A", ",", "to", "compete", "for", "your", "country", ",", "for", "America", ",", "and", "B", ",", "to", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "To win is something that's unimaginable.", "answer_tokens": ["To", "win", "is", "something", "that", "'s", "unimaginable", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "You sympathize with them?", "question_tokens": ["You", "sympathize", "with", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 548, "question": "It was a natural thing?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "a", "natural", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "It was the way that I always ran since I was a kid.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "the", "way", "that", "I", "always", "ran", "since", "I", "was", "a", "kid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 558, "question": "Are you a fan of his style?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "a", "fan", "of", "his", "style", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 559, "answer": "Well, I'm a fan of his speed, that's for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "a", "fan", "of", "his", "speed", ",", "that", "'s", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 565, "question": "He's been saving himself for the big one?", "question_tokens": ["He", "'s", "been", "saving", "himself", "for", "the", "big", "one", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 566, "answer": "I think he's had some trouble this year.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "had", "some", "trouble", "this", "year", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 640, "question": "You think it gives him an advantage?", "question_tokens": ["You", "think", "it", "gives", "him", "an", "advantage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 641, "answer": "I think it does give him an advantage.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "does", "give", "him", "an", "advantage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "I think he probably has earned that advantage, hasn't he?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "probably", "has", "earned", "that", "advantage", ",", "has", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "You can't do that, though.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "ca", "n't", "do", "that", ",", "though", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Do you think he might?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "he", "might", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "No, he's not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "he", "'s", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 664, "question": "Wouldn't it be an amazing moment for the Olympics?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "n't", "it", "be", "an", "amazing", "moment", "for", "the", "Olympics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 665, "answer": "It will be.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "will", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Where are you looking for big American achievement before the end of the games?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "are", "you", "looking", "for", "big", "American", "achievement", "before", "the", "end", "of", "the", "games", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "OHNSON: The sprints are typically where we have always dominated.", "answer_tokens": ["OHNSON", ":", "The", "sprints", "are", "typically", "where", "we", "have", "always", "dominated", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 683, "question": "You still running?", "question_tokens": ["You", "still", "running", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 684, "answer": "I wouldn't call it running.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "call", "it", "running", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Do you like being called the mother of gymnastics?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "being", "called", "the", "mother", "of", "gymnastics", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Thank you very much.", "answer_tokens": ["Thank", "you", "very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "I feel good.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "feel", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 701, "question": "When you walk around here, do you get a good reaction when people realize it's you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "walk", "around", "here", ",", "do", "you", "get", "a", "good", "reaction", "when", "people", "realize", "it", "'s", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 702, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", ":", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Did you really?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "ORBUT: Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["ORBUT", ":", "Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 707, "question": "It all brought it back to you?", "question_tokens": ["It", "all", "brought", "it", "back", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 708, "answer": "I felt like I was 17 again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "felt", "like", "I", "was", "17", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 716, "question": "Was it all easy?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "it", "all", "easy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 717, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 738, "question": "What's the one, if I could relive it for you now, which one would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "one", ",", "if", "I", "could", "relive", "it", "for", "you", "now", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 739, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120801pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 741, "question": "Is that always the best?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "always", "the", "best", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "."], "aSentId": 742, "answer": "Oh, no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]